<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<webtrack>
  <top>
    <num>551</num>
    <title>
      intellectual property
    </title>
    <desc>
      Find documents related to laws or regulations that protect intellectual property.
    </desc>
    <narr>
      Relevant documents describe legislation or federal regulations that protect authors 
      or composers from copyright infringement, or from piracy of their creative work. 
      These regulations may also be related to fair use or to encryption.
    </narr>
  </top>

  <top>
    <num>
      552
    </num>
    <title>
      Foods for cancer patients
    </title>
    <desc>      
      Find foods good for cancer patients.
    </desc>
    <narr>      
      Relevant documents cover foods, types of foods, and diets that
      contribute to the recovery of cancer patients. Information may serve
      consumers, nutritionists, or medical personnel. Exclude pages covering
      foods to prevent cancer.
    </narr>
  </top>
  
  <top>
    <num>
      553
    </num>
    <title>
      federal funding mental illness
    </title>
    <desc>     
      How much does the federal government spend on mental health, and to
      what entities does the funding go?
    </desc>
    <narr>      
      Relevant documents state the entities to which the government
      directs funding for mental health and/or how much money is
      allocated. State spending on mental health is not relevant, unless
      that money came from the federal government. Calls for proposals for
      grants are not relevant. Standards for grantees are not relevant.
    </narr>
  </top>

  <top>
    <num>
      554
    </num>
    <title>
      Home buying
    </title>
    <desc>      
      How does one find and apply for mortgages and buy a first home?
    </desc>
    <narr>      
      Relevant documents school the reader in buying a home and obtaining a
      mortgage.  Documents referring to obtaining low-cost housing but not
      buying a home do not qualify.
    </narr>
  </top>

  <top>
    <num>
      555
    </num>
    <title>
      criteria obtain U.S. visa
    </title>
    <desc>      
      What criteria does the Immigration and Naturalization Service use to
      approve visa applications from foreign nationals?
    </desc>
    <narr>     
      Relevant documents come from the U.S. government stating policy
      on requirements for foreign nationals requesting U.S. visas to receive
      approval. Documents from U.S. consulates abroad or foreign governments
      are not relevant. How U.S. citizens can obtain visas for travel abroad
      are not relevant.
    </narr>
  </top>

  <top>
    <num>
      556
    </num>
    <title>
      Federal food purchasing
    </title>
    <desc>      
      For what purposes does the federal government purchase food?
    </desc>
    <narr>      
      Relevant documents state the agency or entity for which the
      federal government purchases food and the purposes for which it is
      used. Documents regarding state purchasing of food are not relevant.
      Documents informing farmers on how to apply for government purchase of
      commodities are not relevant unless they state the purpose for which
      the government would purchase those commodities.
    </narr>
  </top>

  <top>
    <num>
      557
    </num>
    <title>
      clean air, clean water
    </title>
    <desc>      
      Find documents describing efforts to maintain or improve clean air
      or clean water.
    </desc>
    <narr>      
      Relevant documents include descriptions of legislation or
      regulations to check water and air pollution or to control smog and
      automobile emissions.
    </narr>
  </top>

  <top>
    <num>
      558
    </num>
    <title>
      U.S./Russian Relationship
    </title>
    <desc>      
      Describe the present day relationship between the U.S. and Russia.
    </desc>
    <narr>      
      Relevant documents detail the contemporary status of cooperation and
      the overall relationship between the U. S. and Russia at present,
      including business, trade, financial and in-kind assistance, as well
      as official governmental relations.
    </narr>
  </top>

  <top>
    <num>
      559
    </num>
    <title>
      Federally assisted community volunteer programs
    </title>
    <desc>      
      Find local community volunteer programs for which the federal
      government provides resources.
    </desc>
    <narr>      
      Relevant documents describe local community volunteer programs that
      receive financial assistance, training, or other resources from the
      federal government.  These include national programs with local
      components, e.g., Foster Grandparents, or local programs receiving
      federal assistance, e.g., a service-learning program.  Exclude such
      programs as the Peace Corps and the National Guard.
    </narr>
  </top>

  <top>
    <num>
      560
    </num>
    <title>
      Symptoms of diabetes
    </title>
    <desc>      
      Find documents that list and explain the danger signals of Type I and
      Type II diabetes.
    </desc>
    <narr>      
      Relevant documents give the symptoms/danger signals that
      consumers need to recognize as warnings of the onset of Type I and
      Type II diabetes. Exclude documents directed at medical personnel.
    </narr>
  </top>

  <top>
    <num>
      561
    </num>
    <title>
      Eradication of boll weevils
    </title>
    <desc>      
      Find documents describing how farmers can eradicate boll weevils.
    </desc>
    <narr>      
      Relevant documents report on established eradication programs and
      on research to refine or supplement these. Exclude documents on other
      types of weevils and on the history of the boll weevil in the United
      States.
    </narr>
  </top>

  <top>
    <num>
      562
    </num>
    <title>
      world population growth
    </title>
    <desc>      
      What is the outlook for world population growth?
    </desc>
    <narr>      
      Relevant documents include projections of and discussion of world
      population growth. Growth of individual nations' populations is
      relevant, but data on states within the U.S. is not relevant.
    </narr>
  </top>

  <top>
    <num>
      563
    </num>
    <title>
      smoking drinking during pregnancy
    </title>
    <desc>      
      Find documents describing effects on children of mothers' smoking
      and/or drinking during pregnancy.
    </desc>
    <narr>      
      Relevant documents describe effects on the cognitive, social,
      emotional, or physical status of children (prenatal through adulthood)
      that result from their mothers' smoking or drinking while
      pregnant. Cigarette or alcohol use after the birth of a child is not
      relevant.
    </narr>
  </top>

  <top>
    <num>
      564
    </num>
    <title>
      mother-infant nutrition
    </title>
    <desc>      
      Find documents describing guidelines for good nutrition
      for mothers and infants and/or federal programs to promote their use.
    </desc>
    <narr>      
      Relevant documents describe good nutrition for infants from birth to
      18 months. Those related to older children are not relevant. Programs
      described must be federal, not state or local.
    </narr>
  </top>

  <top>
    <num>
      565
    </num>
    <title>
      Library services for disabled
    </title>
    <desc>      
      Find documents that describe library services for persons with disabilities.
    </desc>
    <narr>      
      Relevant documents will describe major services for the visually
      handicapped in federal, state, or large regional libraries.
      Exclude minor services in small libraries and such
      mandated features as physical access for the wheelchair bound.
    </narr>
  </top>

  <top>
    <num>
      566
    </num>
    <title>
      Television violence
    </title>
    <desc>      
      What is being done about violence on TV?
    </desc>
    <narr>      
      Relevant documents describe actions taken or statements made about
      violence on TV, its effect on children and what is being done or
      should be done about it. Advice to parents to limit TV viewing is not
      relevant.
    </narr>
  </top>

  <top>
    <num>
      567
    </num>
    <title>
      indigenous folk art
    </title>
    <desc>      
      Find documents that describe efforts to promote and preserve
      indigenous folk art.
    </desc>
    <narr>      
      Relevant documents may be related to arts and crafts produced by
      Eskimo (Inuit) and American Indian such as weaving, jewelry,
      sculpture, woodcarving, painting, basketry. Amish, Shaker, and
      Appalachian arts and crafts products are also relevant. Advertisements
      for the sale of particular items are not relevant documents.
    </narr>
  </top>

  <top>
    <num>
      568
    </num>
    <title>
      federal funding art museums
    </title>
    <desc>      
      What types of federal funding are available to support art museums
      throughout the country?
    </desc>
    <narr>      
      Relevant documents are only those that describe grants or other
      funding sources to art museums.  Documents that only describe museum
      programming are not relevant, even if the museum is a federal
      institution.
    </narr>
  </top>

  <top>
    <num>
      569
    </num>
    <title>
      invasive animals and plants
    </title>
    <desc>      
      Find documents related to controlling invasive animals and plants.
    </desc>
    <narr>      
      Relevant documents describe federal nationwide or regional programs
      aiming to control invasive plants and animals that are threatening
      crops, wildlife, or the environment.
    </narr>
  </top>

  <top>
    <num>
      570
    </num>
    <title>
      future occupations
    </title>
    <desc>      
      What occupations will have the greatest need for workers in the next
      10 to 20 years?
    </desc>
    <narr>      
      Relevant documents name categories of jobs and professions where
      there will be the greatest need.  Documents may also give statistics
      showing current employment and projections for future employment.
      Recruitment documents that do not include the above data are not
      relevant.
    </narr>
  </top>

  <top>
    <num>
      571
    </num>
    <title>
      tax havens
    </title>
    <desc>      
      What are tax havens and how are they used and abused?
    </desc>
    <narr>      
      Relevant documents describe "tax havens," locations, usually
      overseas, which have banks where U.S. citizens transfer money to avoid
      U.S. taxes. Relevant would be discussions in Congress on ways to
      discourage use of them.
    </narr>
  </top>

  <top>
    <num>
      572
    </num>
    <title>
      selecting a nursing home
    </title>
    <desc>      
      Describe criteria that one should use in selecting a nursing home.
    </desc>
    <narr>      
      Relevant documents may include formal or informal guidelines,
      checklists, or laws regarding criteria for nursing home care.
    </narr>
  </top>

  <top>
    <num>
      573
    </num>
    <title>
      teaching jobs Europe Asia
    </title>
    <desc>      
      Find documents that list teaching opportunities for Americans in
      Europe and Asia.
    </desc>
    <narr>      
      Only documents that list or describe opportunities for Americans to
      teach in Europe or Asia are relevant.  Teaching opportunities may be
      in any field or with students of any age level.
    </narr>
  </top>

  <top>
    <num>
      574
    </num>
    <title>
      whales dolphins protection
    </title>
    <desc>      
      What efforts are being made nationally and internationally to protect
      whales and dolphins?
    </desc>
    <narr>      
      Relevant documents describe legislation or international agreements to
      protect and save whales and dolphins anywhere in the world.
      Descriptions of the mammals or informational documents from wildlife
      organizations are not relevant unless they include references to
      legislation.
    </narr>
  </top>

  <top>
    <num>
      575
    </num>
    <title>
      Nuclear waste storage transportation
    </title>
    <desc>      
      Find documents that describe how nuclear waste is being stored and how
      it is transported to the storage site.
    </desc>
    <narr>      
      Relevant documents will describe methods of transporting and storing
      nuclear waste.  Documents that describe the benefits or dangers of
      nuclear energy are not relevant; nor are documents in favor of or
      opposed to a particular storage site or means of transportation.
    </narr>
  </top>

  <top>
    <num>
      576
    </num>
    <title>
      Chesapeake Bay ecology
    </title>
    <desc>      
      How are industry and population growth affecting the ecology of the
      Chesapeake Bay?
    </desc>
    <narr>      
      Only documents that show the relationship between local industries,
      (including agriculture,) or population growth in the region and the
      ecology of the Bay are relevant.  A listing of the resources of the
      Bay are not relevant unless they indicate changes in the resources due
      to industry or population changes.
    </narr>
  </top>

  <top>
    <num>
      577
    </num>
    <title>
      Dental school locations
    </title>
    <desc>      
      Find documents that provide the locations of dental schools in the
      United States.
    </desc>
    <narr>      
      Relevant documents will provide the locations of dental schools in the
      U.S., detailed addresses are not required.
    </narr>
  </top>

  <top>
    <num>
      578
    </num>
    <title>
      Regulating zoos
    </title>
    <desc>      
      Describe the federal regulations and oversight of zoos.
    </desc>
    <narr>      
      Any document describing regulations regarding animal or human safety,
      importation of endangered species, humane treatment of animals,
      etc. is relevant.  Information that describes monitoring
      programs is also relevant.  A site displaying zoo events and
      activities is not relevant.
    </narr>
  </top>

  <top>
    <num>
      579
    </num>
    <title>
      US fresh drinking water resources
    </title>
    <desc>      
      Where and how extensive are US fresh drinking water resources?
    </desc>
    <narr>      
      Find documents citing the locations and extent of US fresh drinking
      water resources.  References to the size of populations dependent upon
      particular fresh drinking water resources for consumption are
      relevant.  Documents identifying resources used for recreational
      purposes are not relevant. Problems in water quality of particular
      drinking water resources are not relevant.
    </narr>
  </top>

  <top>
    <num>
      580
    </num>
    <title>
      US immigration history demographics
    </title>
    <desc>      
      What are the history and patterns of immigration to the US since 1900?
    </desc>
    <narr>      
      Graphs, charts, textual material that describes the history and
      patterns of immigration to the US since 1900 are relevant.  Relevant
      material may include countries of origin, regions settled in the US,
      or American immigration laws that govern the number of people entering
      the country.  Documents helping with visas, etc. are not relevant.
    </narr>
  </top>

  <top>
    <num>
      581
    </num>
    <title>
      Lymphoma detection symptoms treatment
    </title>
    <desc>      
      Find documents that provide basic information about non-Hodgkin's lymphoma.
    </desc>
    <narr>      
      Relevant documents will contain information on the definition,
      symptoms, diagnosis, causes, treatment, mortality, survival, etc.  The
      information must pertain to non-Hodgkin's lymphoma.  Information on
      Hodgkin's disease is not relevant.
    </narr>
  </top>

  <top>
    <num>
      582
    </num>
    <title>
      Utah ski resorts
    </title>
    <desc>      
      Find documents that provide the locations of ski resorts in Utah.
    </desc>
    <narr>      
      Relevant documents will locate and/or name ski resorts in Utah, a
      detailed address is not required.
    </narr>
  </top>

  <top>
    <num>
      583
    </num>
    <title>
      Florida's endangered species
    </title>
    <desc>      
      Find what endangered plants and animals live in Florida.
    </desc>
    <narr>      
      Relevant documents list, describe, or discuss endangered plant and
      animal species in Florida. Include documents discussing the Endangered
      Species Act only if these list or discuss Florida's endangered species
      or matters that directly affect them. Exclude documents discussing
      species that are not endangered or do not live in Florida.
    </narr>
  </top>

  <top>
    <num>
      584
    </num>
    <title>
      Birth defects in the US
    </title>
    <desc>      
      Find documents identifying the types, causes, and extent of birth
      defects in the US.
    </desc>
    <narr>      
      Documents identifying environmental factors or citing particular
      behaviors during pregnancy are relevant if linked directly to
      potential defect outcomes. National data and statistics on particular
      birth defects are relevant; similar data/statistics relative to
      individual states or communities are not relevant.
    </narr>
  </top>

  <top>
    <num>
      585
    </num>
    <title>
      Tornado basics
    </title>
    <desc>      
      Find documents that provide basic information about tornadoes.
    </desc>
    <narr>      
      Relevant documents will provide information on the history of
      tornadoes, how tornadoes form, forecasting, the Fujita Intensity
      Scale, specific tornado locations, etc.
    </narr>
  </top>

  <top>
    <num>
      586
    </num>
    <title>
      Women's health cancer
    </title>
    <desc>      
      Find documents providing data on prevention, treatment, and outcomes
      regarding cancers which typically affect women.
    </desc>
    <narr>      
      Relevant documents will associate particular cancers (i.e., ovarian,
      breast, cervical) with women's health especially in the US.
      Statistical data on survival/mortality rates nationwide and
      internationally are relevant.  Prevention and early detection programs
      and progress are relevant.  Medical reports/studies on prognoses,
      treatments, and outcomes are relevant. Data on cancer occurrence,
      programs, and outcomes not specific to cancers which typically affect
      women are not relevant.
    </narr>
  </top>

  <top>
    <num>
      587
    </num>
    <title>
      Bilingual education
    </title>
    <desc>      
      What does research tell us about the effectiveness of bilingual education?
    </desc>
    <narr>      
      Only documents that describe research either on best practices for
      teaching in bilingual classrooms or on the effectiveness of bilingual
      education are relevant.  Grant applications, case studies,
      demographics are not relevant.
    </narr>
  </top>

  <top>
    <num>
      588
    </num>
    <title>
      Golf resort locations
    </title>
    <desc>      
      Find documents that provide the locations of golf resorts.
    </desc>
    <narr>      
      Relevant documents will provide the locations of golf resorts with their
      own golf course and lodging.  Resorts that use nearby golf courses are not
      relevant.  Municipal golf courses are not relevant.
    </narr>
  </top>

  <top>
    <num>
      589
    </num>
    <title>
      Mental Illness in Adolescence
    </title>
    <desc>      
      Find studies about and services offered for mental illness in
      adolescents.
    </desc>
    <narr>      
      Relevant documents refer to studies about different mental conditions
      afflicting some teens or services offered for teens with the
      condition. Documents with information about other health care or
      conditions other than mental, such as pregnancy prevention, are not
      relevant.
    </narr>
  </top>

  <top>
    <num>
      590
    </num>
    <title>
      Pilot training schools
    </title>
    <desc>      
      Find documents that contain the locations of schools for pilot training.
    </desc>
    <narr>      
      Relevant documents will locate schools that provide the training
      required to obtain a license to pilot aircraft such as airplanes,
      helicopters, gliders and airships.  Training for recreational,
      private, or airline transport pilot certificates is relevant.
    </narr>
  </top>

  <top>
    <num>
      591
    </num>
    <title>
      education Indian reservations
    </title>
    <desc>      
      What is the current status of education on Indian reservations.
    </desc>
    <narr>      
      Relevant documents describe programs for education of children and
      young adults on Indian reservations. Education programs that do not
      specifically mention Indian reservations are not relevant.
    </narr>
  </top>

  <top>
    <num>
      592
    </num>
    <title>
      Fuel cell uses
    </title>
    <desc>      
      Find documents that describe the present or planned uses of fuel cells.
    </desc>
    <narr>      
      Relevant documents will describe the types of fuel cells and their
      applications.  Documents that only describe fuel cell technology are
      not relevant.
    </narr>
  </top>

  <top>
    <num>
      593
    </num>
    <title>
      Bush human rights China
    </title>
    <desc>      
      What is the Bush administration's policy on human rights in China?
    </desc>
    <narr>      
      Relevant documents contain statements from President George
      W. Bush or members of his administration relating to human rights in
      China. Statements on proposals to approve China's entrance into the
      World Trade Organization are relevant when they also discuss human
      rights in China. Statements by congressmen and senators are not
      relevant unless they mention Bush administration views.
    </narr>
  </top>

  <top>
    <num>
      594
    </num>
    <title>
      Foods preventing high cholesterol
    </title>
    <desc>      
      Find foods that help people prevent high cholesterol.
    </desc>
    <narr>      
      Relevant documents cover foods, types of foods, and diets that help people
      prevent high cholesterol. Exclude documents covering foods or diets
      for preventing other health problems.
    </narr>
  </top>

  <top>
    <num>
      595
    </num>
    <title>
      girls math education
    </title>
    <desc>      
      What efforts are being made to improve girls' education in the area of math?
    </desc>
    <narr>      
      Relevant documents describe programs in schools that interest
      girls in taking math courses and that help them attain proficiency in
      math.  Special efforts to teach math to boys and girls, where girls
      are specifically mentioned, are relevant. Special efforts to teach
      math, with no mention of girls, are not relevant. Documents that note
      girls' lack of confidence in their math ability but do not say what is
      being done about it are not relevant.
    </narr>
  </top>

  <top>
    <num>
      596
    </num>
    <title>
      Federal Law Enforcement Jobs
    </title>
    <desc>      
      How do you find federal law enforcement job opportunities?
    </desc>
    <narr>      
      Relevant documents talk about jobs that are conceivably open to
      members of the general public. Sites which speak about statistics of
      or training for law enforcement officers are not relevant.
    </narr>
  </top>

  <top>
    <num>
      597
    </num>
    <title>
      IDEA legislation
    </title>
    <desc>      
      Find documents related to changes in special education for children
      with disabilities resulting from IDEA legislation (Individuals with
      Disabilities Education Act).
    </desc>
    <narr>      
      Relevant documents describe current provisions for children with
      disabilities that are a direct response to regulations resulting from
      this legislation. These changes may be related to "inclusion," to
      appropriate materials for testing, for a "free appropriate education,"
      etc.
    </narr>
  </top>

  <top>
    <num>
      598
    </num>
    <title>
      Foreign terrorist organizations
    </title>
    <desc>      
      Find documents naming foreign terrorist organizations and the US
      criteria for their designation as such.
    </desc>
    <narr>      
      Relevant documents identify by name entities designated officially by
      the US as foreign terrorist organizations and/or state the official US
      criteria for so designating such organizations.  Official US
      designations as foreign terrorist organizations are relevant.
      Unofficial or non-US allegations of terrorist activity by foreign
      entities are not relevant.  Documents describing activities of
      entities providing funding or logistical support to foreign terrorist
      organizations are not relevant.
    </narr>
  </top>

  <top>
    <num>
      599
    </num>
    <title>
      scientific research misconduct
    </title>
    <desc>      
      Find documents related to cases of scientific research misconduct
      and/or efforts made to control or discourage such behavior.
    </desc>
    <narr>      
      Relevant documents may be related to Institutional Review Boards
      (IRB), protection of human subjects, or conflicts of interest on the
      part of scientists conducting the research.
    </narr>
  </top>

  <top>
    <num>
      600
    </num>
    <title>
      highway safety
    </title>
    <desc>      
      Find documents related to improving highway safety in the U.S.
    </desc>
    <narr>      
      Relevant documents include those related to the improvement of safety
      of all vehicles driven on highways, including cars, trucks, vans, and
      tractor trailers. Ways to reduce accidents through legislation,
      vehicle checks, and drivers education programs are all relevant.
    </narr>
  </top>
</webtrack>
